Good morning.
>> I'll ask again. How's the conversation
there going?
>> Good.
>> You know, I was telling Bert this on the
way over here. U 2006 was my first
uh first time doing this and and the
first question was about a veteran
quarterback whether he was going to come
back or not. So, it's a big deja vu, but
no, it's it's going good. Um it's been
very positive and we'll just continue to
talk. So, we talk regularly. Were you
confident then and are you the same
level of confident now?
>> That's a great question. Uh it was a
different tone then because I was just a
youngster and and the questions your
your questions are a lot more uh were
very polite compared to the way the
questions were asked back then. So, but
uh yeah, I'm confident, but at the end
of the day, it's a personal decision.
So, uh I think we're in a good space.
>> Mike, you were kind of alluding to this
yesterday. what depending on the city
you're playing, cold weather, Green Bay,
cold weather Pittsburgh as opposed to
warm weather Dallas. Is a type of
quarterback,
bigger, stronger, more physical type of
quarterback necessary? Do you know what
I mean?
>> Well, I I just think it's part of your
preparation, you know, and it's it's
part of your uh it's part of your
planning as far as what your system's
going to look like. Uh because the end
of the day, you know, the most important
games are in December, December and
January. and and to be able to play in
those games in an out outdoor, you know,
it requires to play a certain way and uh
and that's was always evident in my time
in Green Bay. And yeah, there's, you
know, there's things that uh you do for
the surface, you know, the type of shoes
you make sure your guys wear, all all
those little details. Um, those are the
things that I think about and even when
we were talking about player profiles
yesterday, I think that's that's where
the discipline of trying to stay true to
that type of player is important in the
outdoor climates in my opinion.
>> How how similar do you anticipate your
offense being in Pittsburgh to what you
are doing in Green Bay, especially if
Aaron does? Um
I mean similar as in I mean it's going
to be the same offense uh structurally
as far as the beliefs uh the principles
of the philosophical approach the depth
in the details but you know it's very
important in my opinion systematically
if you draft a player that has unique
talents and you say he can't fit he
doesn't fit my system I I've always felt
that you got to take a look at your
system. So, we got to be able to have
room, you know, we got to have a big
enough arrow. So, when Omar and the
personnel, we sit in there and we
decide, you know, to draft these these
young men that that we have we have a
place, you know, for them. Um, everybody
all right.
You good? Okay. All right.
That was funny. Um, so
Oh, is that priorities? I get it. Yeah,
I get it. Okay. Okay. Where the hell
were we?
>> Oh god.
>> System.
>> Yeah. Fin system. So, you know, be
systematic with your players. So, you
So, we all run similar plays. Um, you
know, concept teach. It's just how you
coach them. You know, the the details.
Um, you know, certain receivers have
different skill set to how they run an
option route. So, you know, you got to
tie that option route to the
quarterback's feet. So all those things
we'll be probably closer to the offense
in Dallas than probably what we did in
Green Bay. Um so for for comparable
>> does that similarities and and that kind
of continuity at all help maybe give you
a little bit more flexibility with
Aaron's decision-m timeline that he has
some familiarity with those concepts in
Green Bay.
>> Well, if he was sitting here, I think he
would echo the same thing. The
quarterback room's going to be coached
the same way whether he's in there or
he's not. It's, you know, you coach to
the lead lead player because if you're
going to if you're going to build your
if you take the passing game, if you're
truly going to be tied to the to the
discipline and the footwork and the
teachings of of how that position plays
and it's coordinated with the perimeter,
um you have to get they all have to be,
you know, synchronized. So that that
part won't change. And uh so that that's
why I mean, you know, we we're we're
always looking to I'd have five
quarterbacks if you if you could, you
know, and I I think it's something the
league should consider, but uh you know,
I I don't think you're going to have
enough quarterbacks in your building to
train. So, it's it's it's it's the
starting point of the offense and and
that's the way it's always been and
that's the way we'll be in Pittsburgh.
Oh, definitely. I I I love I love the
fact that their play styles emulate each
other. So, that's what I was real
excited about with Rico, you know,
having to work with Rico. Uh, a big
thing that I I I think is very important
for a running back, the first question I
always ask in the evaluation process,
can he play all three all three downs?
You know, cuz, you know, we all want
four down players. If you're, you know,
you're looking to build a scope of, you
know, particularly the running back
position and linebacker positions, you
know, for value, but, uh, you know,
these guys both can play all three
downs. And that's that's important.
That's and that's real important for a
play caller because you know you want to
push you want to push the envelope you
know get in and out of uh you know
personnel groups. You also want to be
able to stay on the field right you know
go right from second down to third down
go right from third down to fourth down
and no huddle type things. And so having
backs that don't have to come out of the
game on third down. That's that's that's
something that I I put a lot of value
in, you know, and I and I feel that we
got two guys we can just go play
tomorrow with and uh and I'm excited
about those guys.
got at safety. Now you got three guys
safety.
How does that affect? How do you see the
versatility?
>> Yeah, we're going we're staying right
down the same path. You know, we're
talking about player flexibility. Uh
that's really the first conversation I
had with Jaylen. you know, you know,
looking at our defense part from the
offensive perspective, whether you're a
pass rusher or a dynamic, you know,
secondary player, you know, if you can
line up at safety, nickel, dime, and and
jump out the corner in a matchup
situation, there's tremendous value in
that. So, and and that's why, you know,
Brisker, the ability to play multiple
positions, and it's going to be the same
way in the draft. We're having these
same conversations because 17 games is
real. You know, 16 games is a long
season. And you know I you know you
remember when we went from 14 to 16. So
position flex is critical probably in
the offensive line more than any
position in football. I mean I I haven't
had an offensive line you know if you
look at the statistic of five the starts
of the five same offensive lineman the
number of games they start and how it
equates to winning. It's been going on
in our league for decades. So play
player position flexibility is something
that I that I put a lot of value in.
>> Mike. What is the role of Brian Angelico
with you call him plays? How do you guys
>> I mean Angelico Brian is a outstanding
football coach. Um he's he's the
offensive coordinator. Coordinating is
probably the toughest job in the NFL. Um
you know I think you know going along
with the play calling. So to have
someone that's uh like Brian that I'm
aligned with. We've worked we worked
together before. Um you know he's got a
ton of experience. Uh he's a great
teacher. He's a glue guy. Uh his
knowledge base is as high as anybody
you'd sit down and talk football with.
He's been in different systems. So, I
mean, he'll do the everyday coordinator
things and and I'll do it alongside with
him cuz we have to be connected. Um and
you know and so we we spend a lot of
time like I you know we spend a lot of
time talking after the fact you know but
cuz he needs to keep for instance what
I'm saying is we have a meeting schedule
that's set and then um you know we start
at 7:30 and the meeting goes well I may
get pulled out of there so my ability to
jump in and out of there he has to be
able to keep going. So I've done this
before and so that's the way it works
and and I just to think that for me to
have a confidence I have in him in year
one shows what I think of him because I
you know normally that's something you
evolve to just enjoy going play. Do you
ever think about just
something?
>> Oh man way too many cameras for a fun
answer here. Um just uh no I I think the
think calling plays you know jobs
responsibilities you know it's everybody
in in coaching operations you know we
look at everybody that we you know bring
into our building you know everybody has
talents you know everybody has
experience and when you put it all
together you know in in this particular
responsibility we feel it's the best
thing for our football team
Yeah, I think it's unique in a number of
ways. A, you know, because I've been in
the league a long time. Um, you have a
you have a a lot of candidates. The the
Western Pennsylvania NFL connection is
real. Um, there's a there's a lot of
people that are disappointed that not
having the opportunity to to be, you
know, with with the Steelers and I
clearly understand that. So, that was a
challenge. Um, I've always looked at
the, you know, the hiring process. You
know, diversity is something I've always
had in the forefront of my mind, whether
it was, you know, um player, former
player, non former player, you know, um
small college guy. I I I always wanted
my staff to have a level of experience.
Then I had I wanted middle, you know,
like a middle class that can grow to
that position. And I always wanted to
develop young guys. I've always viewed
the coaching staff very similar to the
to the locker room. So, I've always
looked at that. And if you look at the
three staffs that I've hired in Green
Bay, Dallas, and now Pittsburgh, you you
you'll see the diversity in those staffs
because, you know, it's locker rooms.
It's everybody talks about culture and
and the needle of growth is something
that NFL locker rooms are very unique
and I've always tried to emulate that in
developing a coaching staff. While
you're talking about coaching staff, I'm
curious, how much do you plan to be
involved in like all aspects, both sides
of the ball? And how much will there be
autonomy for Patrick Graham to take
command of of that side and the defense?
>> Yeah, just just doing this for quite
some time and and really my first
experience where I felt I was able to
get into the rhythm was with Dom Capers.
Dom was we were together I want to say 9
years 10 years in Green Bay and Dom's an
early morning guy so you know we'd
always have that block of time you know
from like you know 5:00 a.m. 6 6:15 and
set his day and keep keep me in the loop
of what's going on and then also you
know at the end of the night cuz you
know it's off you have to be if you're
going to call the plays you got to be in
the room you got to be in the decision I
have to be in that quarterback room so
you can't be you can't be in all those
places at once and I it's ridiculous to
try so um but you know I've known
Patrick for quite some time um he knows
how I feel about the history of this
defense I I mean, this system's been Dom
Capers, Bill Cower put this system in
1992. You know, Mike Tom has done a
great job carrying it forward. So, we're
looking to build off of what's what's in
place. You know, we're not we're not
throwing away everything and starting
over. So, when our players get there,
they'll see the the variation that we're
teaching and what the beliefs are.
>> Mike, a year removed from Dallas, how do
you look back on that on your tenure
there?
>> Oo. Um,
great experience. I think just like
anything uh especially the last couple
days uh the people you know just some
great people there really enjoyed
working with him as uh Jerry I mean I
got to see him um on Sunday so um I I
miss him in a lot of ways you know so
he's uh I I think I've heard all the
stories 10 times so I think I'm good on
the story storytelling but no the the
family and just the way um you know they
treat the people working there that's
that's definitely something I miss but
um you I'm I'm I'm thankful for all my
experiences. Uh the start was was wild.
I mean, the pandemic year was, you know,
something I, you know, I look back on
it, I didn't I didn't I felt like I
could I could have did a better job. Uh
we just had a lot of balls in the air.
Um but I thought once we got the program
going, you know, I thought we kind of
hit our stride during the second year.
And um I I really like the direction of
the team, you know, you know, when I
left there. I like the draft classes
that we put together. So, I have I have
nothing but uh great things to say about
my experience at Dallas.
>> Mike, broader question, but you've been
in this league a long time. When a team
transitions from a 4-3 defense to a 34
defense, what does it take from a
coaching standpoint from training the
players who have been there and from
getting the right people in there?
>> Well, the biggest thing is the profiles
and really today, you know, it's not
like you're playing a pure 34 or 43.
It's more about, you know, which
techniques you're living in.
you know, if you play the even
techniques, you know, are you are you
going to play a flat stance, you know,
with your D lineman? So, the body type
is very important. You don't want to be
playing flat stance with guys that don't
have the length to do it. So, that's
that's where the the profile part of it
is has been the biggest change. I went
through that in in Green Bay in '09, uh,
when we we we switched from the 4-3 or
08, I guess it was. Yeah, 09. And so,
um, it's that's the part you have to get
right. Can you do it from a personnel
standpoint in one off seasonason or does
it take a couple years to get the right
profiles in there?
>> To be honest with you, it really depends
what's available. I mean, you like to,
you know, you like to and it's a couple
position, but at the end of the day, I
mean, you know, and the leagues is
trending back more towards more base
defense, but it's still a primarily a
subdefense league. And, you know, and
that's as we know is a is really
primarily fourman fronts.
Mike, one of the guys that you retained
on staff from Mike Thomas staff is Tom
Hart. I know you have familiarity with
him from Green Bay, but what is it that
you like about him and the way that he
works with the quarterbacks?
>> You know, Tom Tom made such an
impression on me in his short time um in
Green Bay. You know, him and Aaron, that
was when you you were still able to have
the quarterback school where you'd start
in the middle of March and and uh and he
he was he was awesome. You know, he was
a sponge. No surprise at all that he
went into coaching. I mean, I he was a
natural fit. So, oh, you know, I think
his what he's put together, his career
out, his career is is exciting and and I
think Tom has a a tremendously bright
future. So, um he would he would he
would have definitely been a candidate
even if he wasn't already there. I So,
um I'm excited to to be, you know,
reconnected with Tom and and looking
forward to, you know, getting that
quarterback room right and and having
him on it like I was given that chance a
long time ago. So yeah, Tom Tom's an
excellent coach. Excellent coach. You
know, he's been the head coach. Um, you
know, he's been out of football. I mean,
he's got a such a unique background. You
know, the only thing I, you know, I
don't like about him, he's from
Cleveland. So, but we have, we work
through that. So,
>> how much does it help a guy like Will
Howard, a young guy, to have that
continuity in the position, coach, he
develops?
>> Big time. I mean, uh, that quarterback
coach is so important. I mean, if Aaron
Rogers and you look at guys in their
careers, great quarterbacks pretty much
usually have a great relationship with
their their quarterback coach,
particularly their their first one. You
know, that's a those are foundation
moments, foundation opportunities
um that that you know, Troy Aman, I look
at the way he he he still talks about
North Turner, you know, just so I mean
that you you see it over and over and
over again. So, um, and and and we'll
we'll have that with Tom.
>> Mike, at what point does timing become
an issue with the Aaron's decision, and
are you and he in relative agreement on
that timing?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm not going to really get
into timelines, so we're we're in
constant communication. Um, talked to
him last night, so I mean, so we're um
we're in we're in a good space and and
we're just continue to work through it.
Did you tell him last night 15 questions
about him?
>> No, I didn't.
>> He says hello. So,
>> is he going to show up here and answer
them for himself?
>> We're good. All right, we're good on the
air and questions.
>> Now that you're a couple of months in,
what is your sense of being able to
build a championship contender? This
team's been in a little bit of a rut,
which is why you're in this position.
>> Well, I I I would say the team's in a
rut. the team won the division last
year. So, it's a playoff football team.
Uh I viewed I viewed the team that way
as a fan last year. You know, I was able
to sit back and and I and I watched the
you know, the Steelers, the Cowboys, and
the Packers. I tried to watch all three
teams as a fan just because of the
connection with the three teams. Um you
know, I thought they had some really
good moments and I was just talking to
Nick Herbing about this. I I really like
the vibe of the team coming down the
stretch. I thought they were coming
together and he he was he was telling me
but we were talking about the locker
room. I said I thought you guys really
you know were positioned to make a run
and that's is we've seen it time and
time again if you can you know play good
football and maybe you know your your
lows are not as you know too low and the
eb and flow your team is consistent you
can hit that December stretch you can go
on a playoff run. So that's my opinion
of last year. Um so yeah and and you
have changed. Yeah. And now you turn the
page. It's a, you know, new coaching
staff. It'll be a new system of
operation. So, it's important for us to
connect. Uh, winning's a huge part of
the Pittsburgh Steeler culture. Um,
you know, I'm I'm bringing a winning
process to Pittsburgh and and um we plan
on winning. So,
>> how involved or hands-on do you in the
draft process and has that increased as
you become more established? And how
different is it the three teams you
>> It's been a challenge this year. I love
it. I love that this is uh I'd say the
most involved of the three teams. Um
it's been, you know, I think that's just
probably has gone with the arc of my
career, too. Um you know, Green Bay was
a you know, Ted was was established
general manager. I was a rookie and so
but I I loved our relationship and how
we did personnel then. Um, you know,
Ted's one thing with me was always, um,
you know, I'll never give you a player
that you don't want because, you know,
it's not gonna, you know, there's just
no sense in that. That was, you know,
how he treated those those moments. That
Dallas, the coaches were very involved.
Um, it was a very coach friendly process
there. Um, and it's probably similar to
to Pittsburgh. I mean, our coaching
staff's very involved in it and it's
been uh it's been difficult to be honest
with you because year one's year one. I
mean, there's just so much to do. You
know, I'm a old school believer you go
back and we put page one of the playbook
in. We talk about the huddle, put the
ball in play cadence. We we you know, we
don't just take the old playbook. I
mean, it been very easy for me to just
to put the playbook on the middle of the
table and say this is what we're
running. That's not what we did. Um I'm
trying to keep some of the terminology
for the offensive players. We've been
able to do that for the defensive
players because of the history of the
defense. So we're, you know, we we are
trying to um keep some things that work
for us as a coaching staff that that are
in place there and just try to keep the
the newness to a minimum. So um and
that's timeconuming is my point. So uh
the coaching staff is they they've been
grinding. So uh this next month's going
to be it's it's going to be a lot of
fun, but we'll basically split our day
between trying to get the players
acclimated with our systems and uh we'll
be in the draft meetings, you know, in
the afternoons. when you left Dallas
where kind of leads
you
>> looking forward to work with those guys
you know it's particularly you know I
I'm
aware of their past experience but you
know I mean it's this is like a Catholic
operation you know you go to say three
hill Marys the priest breast everybody's
got a clean slate so let's let's just
get to work I mean all and I you have to
do that with young guys so um and that
so I'm looking forward to you know I
understood what happened, you know, with
him on special teams. And so I've heard
all that. But he's a he's a young man
that obviously, you know, his his draft
value was, you know, what what they what
we think of him. And so I can't really
answer till I till I get my hands on
him. And, you know, but I'm going to
challenge him to be a three- down
player, you know, challenge him to be
special teams player. And so all the all
those things are are part of being a
young running back in this league,
especially with with the two guys in
front of him.
>> Thank you. I'm sorry. talk about the uh
Bill Coward Don Capers blueprint. Where
was it fairly identical and where would
you have seen anything different
blueprinting?
>> I I mean you're talking about the 34
defense you see. Okay. You know,
>> well the base is the same, you know, I
mean tight dog rush, you know, or tight
with the dog rush once now. Um tight dog
10. So because you know cover one and
cover tens there's a different
variation. So but it's the same. It's
the same It's the same call, you know,
and and that was Dom's league call for
as long as I've known him. And Kevin
Green, that's all you ever wanted to
run, you know. So, um, you know, so
that's that base is still there, you
know. So, when we put in the base
defense, you know, the tight front will
go in first. Uh, the form of the under,
you know, will come off of that. So,
there'll be a very similar teaching
progression of how things are things put
in. Dom Capers is is as detailed as a
coach that that I've ever worked with.
You know, I used to worry about our
salary cap. Um cuz Dom would spend so
much money on highlighters. You know, I
was always worried about us going over
the cap cuz you know, he he would uh or
office supplies went through the roof,
you know what I mean? So, but um no, but
Dom was Dom was awesome to work with.
So, there'll be a lot of similar and
it's really, you know, what TA did, too.
with me. So, I mean, I you could always
see the the blueprint of the past has
always been there in my opinion,
competing against those guys.
>> Mike, you guys traded for Michael
Pitman. How do you kind of envision he
and DK working together and what was it
that you liked about him and acquired
>> position flex? You know, I do prefer the
bigger targets. You know, I think it's
common sense. I mean, you look at
completion percentage. You you want your
quarterback north of 70%. You want the
ball distributed. you know, you want 55,
you know, combination of completions and
rushes to be 55 plus a game. So, those
are things that I I believe in of how
you're going to play on offense. And,
uh, that's why, you know, tight ends,
big tight ends that target, you know,
it's easier to throw these passes than
the ones out there. So, um, those are
common sense, uh, practices that I that
I'm that I'm, you know, I keep keep in
touch with. Um, so I the the bigger
receivers, outdoor climate, um, the
ability to to be to be nasty in first
and second down in a run game cuz, you
know, we we sat through the meetings
there with uh, was that Sunday and they
talked about the big plays, you know,
the statistics. I don't know if
everybody here you get copies of all
that, but the the big the big play
numbers are down. So, I mean, that's
something as a coach, you're always
looking to try to enhance your your big
plays opportunities on first and second
down. That obviously comes off off of
the run game. So bigger receivers
definitely help in that area.
>> When you left
those aspects, that's the opportunity to
put big guys into there. What are the
sort of things that we look for besides
the physical traits and maybe what are
some things that you personally consider
a red flag that scare you away from a
guy when you're talking about?
Well, I mean, every place I've worked,
you know, whether it's a,
you know, whether it's an orange dot or,
you know, you know, EQ grade, you know,
your emotional quotient, every how you
look at that. Uh, everybody has a
history. Um, you know, and now with the
with the age of the of the prospects
coming in, you know, you got more 24,
25, 26 year olds. So, so there's more to
look at, but yeah, you're looking at
you're looking for people that that fit
your culture, you know, and that that
that fit Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. So,
um that's that's definitely a big part
of the conversation. So, um I' I've
never really felt um as a head coach of
a football team that you never had
enough talent. I mean, I I I've always
feel that there's enough there. Uh, it's
really the connection, the emotional
connection, uh, that that's how you win
championships. So, so you're definitely
looking for quality people without a
doubt.
>> When you left Alison, did you think
you'd get another chance or did you
think that was it?
>> Um,
yeah. I I you know, I have confidence in
my abilities, but but I'm also
realistic. uh you know,
growing up to sit here and say that uh I
dreamt in, you know, in my my fifth
grade diaries, I I wrote down I wanted
to be the head coach of three NFL teams.
That's that's not true. Um, but no, I I
I've been super blessed um to for the
people that I grew up around, starting
with the way I was raised, uh, the NFL
coaches that, um, that I was able to
train up, the University of Pittsburgh
coaching staff that I was on. So, uh,
you know, so I have a lot of confidence
in my education and my experience
through the league and and and and feel
that, you know, I I would have a lot to
offer to a club, but I'm also um, you
know, I've been around the block a few
times and I'm very comfortable in my own
skin and um, and I'm not going to lie to
you, I I love being a full-time dad.
I've been able to do it twice, you know,
19 and this past year. And um the year
off was was very very rewarding for me.
So, and that's why this this
opportunity, I mean, just the way it
came about, you know, and so um I I had
to I had to come back. I mean, it was it
was a if there's ever a no-brainer, you
know, opportunity in my lifetime, this
this was it. And so, yeah, but
definitely I I have I have a lot of
confidence in my ability. Why do you
think the NFL is skewed toward young
offensive coaches and what do you think
about someone like Monkey getting his
first chance at um
>> you know I I can only go based off
experience. You know being being a young
offensive coach at at a time coming into
the league and understanding you know
you know the way the league was trending
um
our game's about trends you know playing
in coaching scheme you know health and
safety. So I mean that's yeah so I and
now been able to to interview in a
number of places I mean everybody's
looking for something different and and
what I have learned is it's got to fit
you know so whether it's offense defense
I still think people win you win with
people I I don't I don't believe in he
has to be that kind of guy so guy could
be a hell of an offensive coach but he
might not fit in one organization as
good as he fits in another organization.
I I I think that's real, you know, and
that's been my that's been my
experience. That's my opinion,
>> guys. Two more here. We got to get them
going.
>> You mentioned earlier that you kind of
view the coaching staff.
You want to throw young guys
that kind of
relationship like?
>> Yeah, Brian, you know, I'm going to
consider Bri Brian just he needed a he
needed just a reset that year as a
consultant. I I thought I thought
thought a he was a a tremendous asset
for us. Um you know, we had Ben Mcadoo
do it the year before. So to have that
level of coach in that position was a
true benefit and and I and I think he
really enjoyed it. You know, he enjoyed
being on the defensive side of the ball.
So it was it was it was an able for
opportunity for him to to look through
that lens for a year and he gave Dan
Quinn great input. So I mean it was
awesome doing it. He just needed a reset
for his family and and frankly I just
went through the same thing in 19. I
thought it was I thought it was really
good for him, you know, personally,
really good for his family and and look
what it did. It springboarded him right
back in as an offensive coordinator. I
thought he did a great job for us and uh
so well deserving of his opportunity in
Dallas. So, and um if there's ever been
a guy that's ready, it's it's definitely
Brian Sh. Mike, you've talked on a
number of occas
what what you like about Will Howard.
>> Where will he need to develop the most
to reach his full potential?
>> I think the biggest thing with Will and
it's probably, you know, consistent with
young quarterbacks, they got to win from
the pocket. At the end of the day, you
know, nine 10 games a year are going to
come down to the two-minute drill.
That's that's what the stats tell you.
That's the way we train. So, his ability
to win from the bucket cuz I think he
has everything else. I mean, I people
get caught up on, you know, what round
he went in, but if I was drafting
players uh that year, he wouldn't have
been around in the fifth or sixth round.
I mean, I I I I valued him higher than
that based off Kansas State. And man, he
just I thought he jumped jumped out of
the TV set during the college playoffs.
I mean, I I mean, what is there not to
like about the guy? So, um I think he's
definitely a real prospect as a starting
quarterback. I I I believed that when he
came out. I I don't you know, so you can
talk about his strong emote. You can
talk about some things throwing the
ball. Um I think there's a lot of a lot
of growth with his feet, you know, like
a lot of these guys that and the the
challenge I see in college football,
it's so scheme heavy and they're running
these quarterbacks and their and their
and their schemes are diverse. There's
not a lot of training in the footwork.
So throwing the ball and you got the
best guy that probably has ever done it
in Aaron Rogers. I mean, you look at the
way Aaron throws. I mean, just watch his
feet, you know, watch the ground force,
you know, explosion that comes up
through his feet, through his hips, into
his throwing motion. So, and um so there
my point is there's room for development
there. So, um I think there's a lot to
work with Will. I'm excited. I'm excited
to work with him. You make wood.